Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America Records WAG.235
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Files of Michael J. Quill, 1928-1970.
  - Subseries I:A: TWU Presidential Files, 1928-1970
    - American Federation of Municipal Transit Workers, undated; 1945 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - American Irish Defense Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - American Labor Party, 1936-1938 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - American League: Baseball Pass, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - American League for Peace and Democracy, 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - American Society for Russian Relief, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - American Student Union, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - American Transit Association: "1948 Transit Operations in Cities over 1,000,000 Population", 1949 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - American Transit Association: Report on Labor Practices (I), 1950 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - American Transit Association: Report on Labor Practices (II), 1950 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - American Transit Association: Report on Labor Practices (III), 1950 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - American Youth Congress, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Anti-Communist and Anti-Semitic Materials, 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Anti-War and Anti-Semitic Material (Various Organizations), undated; 1939 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Anti-Nazi / Anti-War Groups, undated; 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Beale, Cecil: Correspondence, 1937-1945 (Box 1a, Folder 1)
    - Beame, Abraham, 1969 (Box 1a, Folder 2)
    - Benefits: TWU, General, undated (Box 1a, Folder 3)
    - Biberman, Herbert, 1965 (Box 1a, Folder 4)
    - Board of Transportation: Clerical Workers Organizing Campaign, 1937-1938 (Box 1a, Folder 5)
    - Bridges, Harry, 1941 (Box 1a, Folder 6)
    - Browder, Earl: Imprisonment, 1941 (Box 1a, Folder 7)
    - Buffalo, NY: Railroad Organizing, 1938 (Box 1a, Folder 8)
    - Building: 153 West 64th Street, 1938-1944 (Box 1a, Folder 9)
    - Bulletin Material, 1936-1942 (Box 1a, Folder 10)
    - Bulletin Material, 1943-1949 (Box 1a, Folder 11)
    - Byrd Committee (Federal Expenditures), 1941 (Box 1a, Folder 12)
    - California Offices, 1943-1947 (Box 1a, Folder 13)
    - Canadian Brotherhood of Railway Workers, Canadian Congress of Labor (CCL), 1943-1944 (Box 1a, Folder 14)
    - Carey, James B., 1955 (Box 1a, Folder 15)
    - Cartoons, 1934-1978 (Box 1a, Folder 16)
    - Case, Walter: International Representative, 1944-1945 (Box 1a, Folder 17)
    - Cassidy, John: International Representative, 1944-1945 (Box 1a, Folder 18)
    - Catholic Church and the TWU: General, undated; 1937; 1947 (Box 1a, Folder 19)
    - Catholic Church: Attack on TWU, 1943 (Box 1a, Folder 20)
    - Catholic Church: "The Church Belongs with the People" (Unidentified Manuscript), [1937-1938] (Box 1a, Folder 21)
    - Celler, Emanuel, 1948 (Box 1a, Folder 22)
    - Chicago Organizing, 1943 (Box 1a, Folder 23)
    - Chicago Regional Office, 1944; 1946 (Box 1a, Folder 24)
    - Child Care Council of Woodside, 1944 (Box 1a, Folder 25)
    - Citizens Budget Commission, May 1905 (Box 1a, Folder 26)
    - Citizenship Cases, 1941-1942 (Box 1a, Folder 26a)
    - Citizenship Cases: Lists of Individuals, 1941-1942 (Box 1a, Folder 27)
    - Civic Associations: List, undated; 1937 (Box 1a, Folder 27a)
    - Civil Rights: Birmingham, AL, 1963 (Box 1a, Folder 28)
    - Civil Rights: Birmingham, AL (Clippings), 1963 (Box 1a, Folder 29)
    - Civil Rights: Columbia, TN (Incidents), 1946 (Box 1a, Folder 30)
    - Civil Rights: General, 1956-1966 (Box 1a, Folder 31)
    - Civil Rights: General (Clippings), 1956-1961 (Box 1a, Folder 32)
    - Civil Rights: General (Clippings), Jan-Aug 1962 (Box 1a, Folder 33)
    - Civil Rights: General (Clippings), Sep-Nov 1962 (Box 1a, Folder 34)
    - Civil Rights: General (Clippings), Jan-Jul 1963 (Box 1a, Folder 35)
    - Civil Rights: General (Clippings), Aug-Nov 1963 (Box 1a, Folder 36)
    - Civil Rights: General (Clippings), 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Civil Rights: Labor, Employment, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights: Mack Charles Parker Lynching, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights: March on Washington (Clippings), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Civil Rights: Selma, AL March, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Civil Rights: Selma, AL (clippings), 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Civil Rights: Student Voice (Atlanta, GA), 1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Civil Rights: TWU Pamphlets, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Clark, George Henry: "The Plan" (Pamphlet), 1951 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Committee to Investigate Local 100 Referendum, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Communism: Michael Quill Statements, 1938-1940; 1948; 1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Communism and the TWU, 1937-1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Communism and the TWU: Anti-Communist Group in Local 100 (IRT) and Dies Committee, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Communism/Anti-Communism: TWU Internal Dispute and Public Response, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Con Edison/ Transfer of Power Plants, 1960-1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Con Edison and UTW Local 1-2: Charges of Discrimination, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO), 1937 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - CIO, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - CIO, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - CIO, Jan-Jul 1940 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - CIO, Aug-Dec 1940 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - CIO, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - CIO, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - CIO, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - CIO, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - CIO, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - CIO, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - CIO, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - CIO, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - CIO, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - CIO, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - CIO, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - CIO: Affiliated Unions, 1943-1946 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - CIO: Affiliated Unions, 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - CIO: American Communications Association Hearing, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - CIO: Committee on Housing, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - CIO: Committee on Housing, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - CIO: Committee on Housing, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - CIO: Committee on Housing, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - CIO: Convention, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - CIO: Convention (Resolution on Ireland), 1944 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - CIO: Convention, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - CIO: Convention, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - CIO: Convention, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - CIO: Convention, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - CIO: Convention, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - CIO: Education Department, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - CIO: Executive Board Meetings, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - CIO: Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - CIO: Greater New York CIO Council, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - CIO: Greater New York CIO Council, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - CIO: Greater New York CIO Council, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - CIO: Greater New York CIO Council, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - CIO: Greater New York CIO Council, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - CIO: Greater New York CIO Council, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - CIO: Greater New York CIO Council, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - CIO: Greater New York CIO Council, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - CIO: Greater New York CIO Council, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - CIO: Greater New York Industrial Union Council, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - CIO: International Affairs, 1949-1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - CIO: International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE) vs. United Electrical Workers (UE), National Labor Relations Board Election, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - CIO: International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Investigation, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - CIO: John V. Riffe, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - CIO: Mike Quill Statement on Political Action, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - CIO: New York City CIO Council, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - CIO: New York City CIO Council, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - CIO: New York City CIO Council, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - CIO: New York City CIO Council, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - CIO: New York City Industrial Union Council, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - CIO: New York State CIO Council, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - CIO: New York State CIO Council Convention, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - CIO: New York State CIO Council Special Convention, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - CIO: New York State Industrial Union Council (later New York State CIO Council), 1938-1949 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - CIO: Political Action Committee, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - CIO: Political Action Committee, 1944-1946; 1951 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - CIO: Regional, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - CIO: Regional, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - CIO: Regional, 1940-1942; 1953-1955 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - CIO: Resolutions and Reports, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - CIO: Social Security Legislation, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - CIO: United Public Workers of America (UPWA) Case, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - CIO: Walter Reuther, 1952-1955 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - CIO: Washington-Baltimore Organizing, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE), 1960-1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Congress of Racial Equality (Clippings), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut Railway and Lighting Co.: Organizing (McGowan Correspondence), 1945 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Connolly Commemorations, undated; 1941-1947 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Connolly, James, undated; 1944 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Contributions, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Convention, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Convention: Correspondence, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Convention: Delegates, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Convention: Proceedings (I), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Convention: Proceedings (II), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Convention: Proceedings (III), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Convention: Resolutions, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Convention, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Convention: Correspondence with Speakers, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Convention: Reports, Rules of Order, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Convention: Resolutions, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Convention: Speeches, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Convention, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Convention: Correspondence with Speakers, Greetings, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Convention: Reports, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Convention: Resolutions (Includes correspondence), 1941 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Convention: Speeches, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Convention, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Convention: Resolutions, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Convention: Speeches, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Convention, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Convention: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Convention: Proceedings (I), 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Convention: Proceedings (II), 1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Convention: Proceedings (III), 1946 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Convention: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Convention: Delegates, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Convention: Election of International Officers, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Convention: Proceedings (I), 1948 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Convention: Proceedings (II), 1948 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Convention: Proceedings (III), 1948 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Convention: Proceedings (IV), 1948 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Convention: Publicity, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Convention: Reports, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Convention: Resolutions, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Convention: Speeches, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Convention, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Convention, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Convention: Proceedings (I), 1950 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Convention: Proceedings (II), 1950 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Convention: Proceedings (III), 1950 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Condolence Letters, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Cranks, Hate Mail, undated; 1941-1955 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Cranks, Hate Mail, 1957-1965 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: General, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: General, 1932-1936 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: General (A-K), 1937 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: General (L-W), 1937 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: General (A-K), 1938 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: General (L-W), 1938 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: General, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: General (A-F), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: General (G-N), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: General (O-Z), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: General, Jan-Jun 1941 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: General, Jul-Dec 1941 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: General, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: General, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: General, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: General, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: General, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: General, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: General, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: General, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: General, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: General, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: General, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: General, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: General, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: General, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: General, 1956-1959 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: General, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: General, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: General, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: General, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Labor-Related Organizations, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Legislative, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Legislative, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Locals, 1941-1951 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Locals, 1955-1956; 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Members, undated; 1935; 1938 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Members, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Members, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Members, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Members, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Members, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Members, 1944-1946 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Members, 1947-1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Members, 1950-1959 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Members in the Military, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Members in the Military (I), 1943 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Members in the Military (II), 1943 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Members in the Military (I), 1944 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Members in the Military (II), 1944 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Members in the Military, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Michael Quill, Political, 1936-1939 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Michael Quill, Political (I), 1940 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Michael Quill, Political (II), 1940 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Michael Quill, Political (III), 1940 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Michael Quill, Political (I), 1941 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Michael Quill, Political (II), 1941 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Michael Quill, Political (III), 1941 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Michael Quill, Political, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Other Unions, undated; 1936 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Other Unions, 1937-1944 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Other Unions (A-O), 1941 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Other Unions (P-Z), 1941 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Other Unions, 1951; 1965 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Postcards, 1937-1941 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Youth Organizations, 1939-1941 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Coughlin, Father James, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Credit Union, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Cripps, Stafford, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Cuban Hospitals Fund, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Daily Activity Reports, 1936; 1937 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Dairy Farmers Union: Journal, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1937 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Dies Committee, 1938-1940 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Dubinsky, David, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Douglas, Helen Gahagan, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Education Program (TWU), 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Faber, Gustav: Resolution (humorous), 1940 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Fare Dispute: Brooklyn Communist Party, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Finances, 1930-1939 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Finances, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Finances, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Finances, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Finances, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Finances, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Finances, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Finances, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Finances, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Finances, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Finances, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Finances, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Finances, 1951; 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Finances: Audit Reports, Jul 1937-Dec 1938 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Finances: Audit Reports, Apr-05 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Finances: Audit Reports, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Finances: Audit Reports, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Finances: Audit Reports, Jan-Nov 1942 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Finances: Audit Reports, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Finances: Audit Reports, Apr 1944-Dec 1945 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Finances: Audit Reports, Nov 1946-Aug 1948 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Finances: Bank Statements, May-05 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Finances: Bank Statements, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Finances: Contributions, 1948-1951 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Finances: Locals, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Financial Reports, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Financial Reports (I), 1949 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Financial Reports (II), 1949 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Financial Reports, 1951 (Box 11a, Folder 1)
    - Fitzsimon, James (International Vice-President), 1945 (Box 11a, Folder 2)
    - Florida: Jack Ryan, Charles Smolikoff Correspondence, 1948-1956 (Box 11a, Folder 3)
    - Forge, Maurice, 1936; 1944-1946 (Box 11a, Folder 4)
    - Foster, William Z., 1949 (Box 11a, Folder 5)
    - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, 1937-1938 (Box 11a, Folder 6)
    - Goldberg, Arthur J., 1953-1959 (Box 11a, Folder 7)
    - Government Contracts: Samples, 1940 (Box 11a, Folder 8)
    - Greater New York Fund, undated (Box 11a, Folder 9)
    - Greater New York Industrial Union Council, 1940-1942 (Box 11a, Folder 10)
    - Greater New York Industrial Union Council, 1943-1944 (Box 11a, Folder 11)
    - Greater New York Industrial Union Council: Legislative Bulletin, 1941-1942 (Box 11a, Folder 12)
    - Greater New York Industrial Union Council: Minutes, Jan 1941- Feb 1942 (Box 11a, Folder 13)
    - Greater New York Industrial Union Council: New York [Harry] Bridges Defense Committee, 1941 (Box 11a, Folder 14)
    - Greater New York Industrial Union Council: Resolutions, 1941-1942 (Box 11a, Folder 15)
    - Greater New York Industrial Union Council: Saul Mills Correspondence, 1941-1944 (Box 11a, Folder 16)
    - Greece, 1941 (Box 11a, Folder 17)
    - Greek Maritime Workers, 1949 (Box 11a, Folder 18)
    - Grogan, William, 1944-1945 (Box 11a, Folder 19)
    - Guinan, Matthew, 1947 (Box 11a, Folder 20)
    - Hays, Arthur Garfield, 1943 (Box 11a, Folder 21)
    - Heron, Ina Connolly to MJQ, 1952 (Box 11a, Folder 22)
    - Hirsch, Henry, 1943-1945 (Box 11a, Folder 23)
    - Histadrut, 1948 (Box 11a, Folder 24)
    - Hogan, Austin, 1942 (Box 11a, Folder 25)
    - Hogan, Austin: Correspondence, 1936 (Box 11a, Folder 26)
    - Hogan, Austin: Correspondence, 1937 (Box 11a, Folder 27)
    - Hogan, Austin: Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 11a, Folder 28)
    - Hogan, Austin: Farewell Dinner, 1942 (Box 11a, Folder 29)
    - Holy Name Labor School, 1947 (Box 11a, Folder 30)
    - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union, Local 1: Dining Room Employees, 1955 (Box 11a, Folder 31)
    - I Am an American Day (includes Fiorello LaGuardia correspondence), 1944 (Box 11a, Folder 32)
    - Impelliteri, Vincent, 1949 (Box 11a, Folder 33)
    - Independent Traction Workers Union, 1937 (Box 11a, Folder 34)
    - Independent Transit Club, Undated (Box 11a, Folder 35)
    - Insurance, 1944-1946 (Box 11a, Folder 36)
    - Interborough Rapid Transit (IRT), 1935-1938 (Box 11a, Folder 37)
    - International Association of Machinists (IAM), 1936-1937 (Box 11a, Folder 38)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Milk Wagon Drivers, undated; 1940 (Box 11a, Folder 38a)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): James Hoffa, 1956-1965 (Box 11a, Folder 39)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1951-1956 (Box 11a, Folder 40)
    - ICFTU: First General Council Meeting (Berlin), 1952 (Box 11a, Folder 41)
    - ICFTU: First World Congress (Free World Labor Conference) (London), 1949 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - ICFTU: Second World Congress (Milan), 1951 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - ICTFU: Third World Congress (Stockholm), 1953 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - ICTFU: Fourth World Congress (Vienna), 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - International Executive Board, 1934-1937 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - International Executive Board, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - International Executive Board, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - International Executive Board, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - International Executive Board, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - International Executive Board, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - International Executive Board, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - International Executive Board, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - International Executive Board, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - International Executive Board, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - International Executive Board, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - International Executive Board, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - International Executive Board, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - International Executive Board, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - International Executive Board, 1956; 1960 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - International Executive Board: Election, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - International Executive Council and Executive Board, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - International Executive Council and Executive Board, 1956; 1960 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - International Longshoremen's Association: Strike, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - International Transport Workers Federation, 1946-1954 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - International Transport Workers Federation II, 1949-1956 (Box 13, Folder 1a)
    - International Transport Workers Federation: 23rd Congress, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - International Transport Workers Federation: Press Report, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1960-1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Ireland: Correspondence with, undated; 1934-1947 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Ireland: Correspondence with, 1947-1955; 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 5a)
    - Ireland: Irish Workers Weekly, Premier Issue, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Ireland: Labour Party, 1937-1950 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Ireland: Leaflets from Ireland, undated; 1931-1938; 1940; 1944-1946; 1950 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Ireland: Memorabilia, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)